sottopelletherapy.com 2015-10-17

# SottoPelle® Bio-Identical Hormone Replacement Therapy: Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting our website (the â€œSiteâ€). We provide this Privacy Statement to highlight our policies with regard to the privacy of information we may gather through your use of this Site. 

1\. COLLECTION OF PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION 

We only collect personally identifiable information when you provide it to us in connection with a request for more detailed information about this Site, its services, or if you provide personally identifiable information in order to use certain functions provided on our Site. For example, if you would like us to send you or someone else more information about this Siteâ€™s services or you seek to purchase any products advertised on the Site, we may ask that you provide us with your name/otherâ€™s name, your/otherâ€™s e-mail address, your/other companyâ€™s name, and your companyâ€™s address so that we may deliver the information to you. 

2\. USE OF PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION; OPTING OUT 

We use the personally identifiable information that you provide over the Site to send you the information you requested or in association with your purchase of products advertised on the Site, to send you notices or other information about this Site, or for any other lawful purpose. We do not, however, share personally identifiable information with third parties without your consent, unless for some reason it becomes necessary to do so to comply with applicable laws or to enforce our rights 

Even after you have requested information from us and have provided us with personally identifiable information such as that discussed in Section 1 above, you may later choose not to continue to receive such information from us by sending a message via our contact page and requesting that either your information be updated with new information, or that such information be completely deleted from our database. Once we have received your request to update or remove your personally identifiable information, we will use commercially reasonable efforts to delete your personally identifiable information from our database (â€œOpting Outâ€). If you Opt Out, you will no longer receive information from us. This Privacy Statement does not, however, apply to other Internet websites that are not under our control (â€œThird-Party Websitesâ€), or to other third parties. You should contact such entities directly regarding their use of your information. 

3\. PROTECTION OF PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION 

We do not make available to the general public any personally identifiable information you provide to us in connection with your request over the Site for information or in association with your purchase of products advertised on the Site. Notwithstanding the foregoing, the transmission of personally identifiable information between you and the Site may not be encrypted and may not be secure. While we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information transmitted to, from, or over the Site, and you do so at your own risk. 

4\. LINKS TO THIRD-PARTY SITES 

The Site may provide links to Third-Party Websites that are not under our control. If you click on a link to such a Third-Party Website, you will be transported to one of these Third-Party Websites and away from this Site. THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT APPLIES TO THIS SITE ONLY, AND IS NOT INTENDED TO DESCRIBE THE PRIVACY POLICIES OF THIRD-PARTY WEBSITES WITH REGARD TO THE COLLECTION AND USE OF PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION; THIS SITE IS NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR THE PRIVACY PRACTICES OF THIRD-PARTY WEBSITES. IF YOU CLICK ON A LINK TO A THIRD-PARTY WEBSITE, YOU SHOULD REVIEW THE PRIVACY STATEMENT AND OTHER TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF SUCH THIRD-PARTY WEBSITE, IF ANY, TO DETERMINE THAT THIRD PARTY WEB SITEâ€™S PRACTICES WITH REGARD TO THE COLLECTION AND USE OF PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION. Any link on the Site to a Third-Party Website does not imply an endorsement of the privacy practices of such Third-Party Website by us, and no such Third-Party Website is authorized to make any representation or warranty on our behalf. 

5\. NON-PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION 

During your visit to the Site, we may use your Internet Protocol (â€œIPâ€) address to help us administer the Site. Also, our server may place small temporary text files called â€œcookiesâ€ on your computerâ€™s processor or in the browser directory of your hard drive. We use your IP address and/or cookies to gather non-personally identifiable demographic information, such as how many users visited a certain part of the Site, but not to track a specific IP address to the identity of a particular individual user. You may choose not to accept cookies by setting your web browser to either refuse all cookies or to notify you each time before a cookie is set. 

6\. THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT MAY CHANGE 

This Privacy Statement may change from time to time. This Site reserves the right to change it without notice to you, so you should review and print it periodically. 

If you believe that this Site has in some way not complied with the policies outlined in this Privacy Statement, or if you have any other questions relating to privacy, please let us know by sending a message detailing your concern via our contact us page.
